Guide to the Media Services Audio and Video Recordings, 1963 - ongoing UA.10.03.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Video Recordings, 1980-2005, undated; 1
  - Commencement Ceremonies, 1984-2003; 1.4
    - Graduation Edit Master 1 of 2, 1987; 3/4-inch (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0017)
    - Graduation Edit Master 2 of 2, 1987; 3/4-inch (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0018)
    - Graduation Exercises Camera Original 1 of 3, 1988 May 08; 3/4-inch (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0019)
    - Graduation Exercises Camera Original 2 of 3, 1988 May 08; 3/4-inch (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0020)
    - Graduation Exercises Camera Original 3 of 3, 1988 May 08; 3/4-inch (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0021)
    - Graduation Exercises Edit Master with TC 1 of 2, 1988 May 08; 3/4-inch (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0022)
    - Graduation Exercises Edit Master with TC 2 of 2, 1988 May 08; 3/4-inch (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0023)
    - Ted Koppel: Commencement, 1987 May 10; VHS (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0041)
  - Productions, 1988-1995, undated; 1.5
    - Duke University Today, 1988; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0001)
      12 minutes
    - Living History: Cuban Missile Crisis, undated; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0004)
      Narration: Alex Roland
    - Living History: Elie Wiesel, 1987 September 15; 3/4-inch (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0008)
    - Living History: Tribute to Angier Biddle Duke, undated; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0003)
      16:45 minutes
    - Year at Duke: Duke Undergrad Admissions, undated; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0002)
      28:45 minutes
    - Yearlook, 1995; 3/4-inch (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0007)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980-1990, undated; 1.6
    - Archive tape, undated; 3/4-inch (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0005)
    - Graphics, circa 1980-1990; 3/4-inch (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0006)
    - Helicopter Footage, circa 1980-1990; 3/4-inch (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0003)
    - J. Walter Thompson Photo Ad Archives B-Roll, 1995 November 2; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0005)
    - Stock Footage: Gardens, circa 1980-1990; 3/4-inch (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0001)
    - Stock Footage: West Campus, 1984 November 10; 3/4-inch (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0002)
- Audio Recordings, 1963-2000, undated; 2
  - Campus Events, 1980-1991; 2.1
    - Alumni Admissions Forum, 1990 July 13; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0004)
    - Alumni Admissions Forum, 1990 July 13; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0005)
    - Alumni Admissions Forum, 1990 July 13; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0006)
    - Alumni Admissions Forum, 1990 July 13; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0007)
    - Alumni Admissions Forum, 1990 July 13; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0008)
    - Alumni Admissions Forum, 1990 July 13; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0009)
    - Alumni Admissions Forum, 1990 July 13; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0010)
    - Alumni Admissions Forum Program, 1990 July 13 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Archibald Cox Address to Duke Law School Class of 1981, audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0003)
    - Basketball: Duke Basketball Team Returns, NCAA Champs, 1991 April 2; digital audio tape (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-DAT-0001)
    - Billy Graham, Duke University Chapel, 1985 November 17; 1/4-inch (Box 10, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0002)
      1 sound tape reel: 10 in.
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration Program, 1980 October 22 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration, Duke University Chapel, 1980 October 22; 1/4-inch (Box 10, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0001)
    - Livingston/Rutgers Jazz with Dizzy Gillespie, Page Auditorium, 1980 Summer; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0002)
    - Preservation Hall Jazz Band, Page Auditorium, 1977 February 4; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0001)
    - Service of Worship Program, 1985 November 17 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Productions, 1978-2000, undated; 2.2
    - Benefits, 1994 January 28; 1/4-inch (Box 10, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0004)
    - Benefits, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 10, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0007)
    - Benefits Orientation Slide Show Narration, 1995 May 22; digital audio tape (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-DAT-0002)
    - Benefits: Duke Biweekly Employee Benefits, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0013)
      1 sound tape reel: 7 in.
    - Benefits: Duke Biweekly Employee Benefits, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0014)
    - Benefits: Duke University Benefits Program, 1990 November 15; 1/4-inch (Box 10, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0003)
    - Benefits: Phylis Profer, 1995 October 23; 1/4-inch (Box 10, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0005)
    - Benefits: Phylis Profer, 1994 December; 1/4-inch (Box 10, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0006)
    - Benjamin N. Duke: Celebration of the Life of Benjamin N. Duke, 1979 February 22; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0022)
    - Benjamin N. Duke: Remembering Ben Duke, undated; audiocassette (Box 11, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0015)
      Duplication master
    - Benjamin N. Duke: Remembering Ben Duke, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0023)
    - Benjamin N. Duke: Remembering Ben Duke, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0024)
    - Bryan Center Slide Show, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0016)
    - Carillon: Pre-Repair Reference Recording Post Repair, 1992 May 14, 1992 October 26; digital audio tape (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-DAT-0003)
    - Chamber of Commerce: Durham, City of Medicine, 1983 February; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0017)
    - Chamber of Commerce: Durham, City of Medicine, 1983 February; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0018)
    - Cheerleaders, 1989 August 10; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0019)
    - Children's Classic, 1979; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0011)
      Archie Campbell, Tom Sullivan, Woody Woodbury, P. Hayes, M. Healy, Forrest Tucker, A. Freeman, Eubie Blake, Professor Irwin Corey, Perry Como
    - Children's Classic, 1979; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0012)
    - Choriocarcinoma Slide Show, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0064)
    - Class of '39, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0020)
    - Class of '39, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0021)
    - Cornelius Eady, 1994 May 19; 1/4-inch (Box 10, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0008)
    - Davison Society, 1979; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0013)
    - Davison Society, 1979; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0014)
    - Earbook, 1981; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0025)
    - Earbook, 1981; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0026)
    - Earbook, 1981; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0027)
    - Earbook, 1981; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0028)
    - Earbook, 1981; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0029)
    - Earbook, 1981; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0064)
    - Earbook, 1981; 1/4-inch (Box 10, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0148)
    - Earbook, 1981; 1-inch (Box 10, Video-reel UA10030003-Vid-0001)
    - Fall Dance, 1985; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0030)
    - Freshman Orientation Slide Show, 1983 January; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0031)
    - Gifts to Endowments: Taking Life Insurance out of the Closet, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0032)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie: Orientation, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0015)
    - Hospital Fire Safety Slide Show, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0033)
    - Hospital Public Relations Radio Spots, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0034)
    - John Hope Franklin: My Recent Visit to Xanadu, 1998 September 30; digital audio tape (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-DAT-0004)
    - KKG Show, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0035)
    - Lutheran Campus Ministry, 1982 May; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0038)
    - Lutheran Campus Ministry, 1982 May; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0039)
    - Marjorie Scheer: The Occupation, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0064)
    - Marjorie Scheer: The Wavering, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0065)
    - Michael Rush Project: Le Cirque du Temps, 1990; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0041)
    - Michael Rush Project: Le Cirque du Temps, 1990; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0042)
    - Michael Rush Project: Le Cirque du Temps, 1990; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0043)
    - Michael Rush Project: Le Cirque du Temps, 1990; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0044)
    - Nathan Womack Interview, 1971 December 9; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0076)
    - Nathan Womack Interview, 1971 December 9; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0077)
    - Nursing School History Slide Show, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0010)
    - Nursing School History Slide Show, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0147)
    - PBC Live: Cotton, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0045)
    - Personal Hygiene and Dress Code, 1982 August; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0046)
    - Poison Control Center Slide Show, 1982 March; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0047)
    - Poison Control Center Slide Show, 1982 March; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0048)
    - Public Relations: Civitan Appeal, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0040)
    - Reynolds Price: Acoustiguide, 1996 October 8; digital audio tape (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-DAT-0006)
    - Reynolds Price: Master Takes NPR, 1995; digital audio tape (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-DAT-0005)
    - Reynolds Price: The Gospel According to Mark, 2000 April 17; digital audio tape (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA10030003-DAT-0007)
    - School of Forestry Slide Show, 1986-1987; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0066)
    - School of Forestry Slide Show, 1986-1987; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0067)
    - School of Forestry Slide Show, 1986-1987; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0068)
    - School of Forestry Slide Show, 1986-1987; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0069)
    - State Employees Credit Union: Assembly Master, 1980 May; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0070)
    - State Employees Credit Union: Mixdown Master, 1980 May; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0071)
    - Structure House Introduction: Dr. Gerard J. Musante, 1995 September 29; digital audio tape (Box 12, Audio-cassette UA10030003-DAT-0008)
    - Structure House Master, 1997 June 24; digital audio tape (Box 12, Audio-cassette UA10030003-DAT-0009)
    - Student Labor Slide Show: Assembly Master, 1982 November; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0072)
    - Student Labor Slide Show: Final Mix, 1982 November; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0073)
    - Talking Books: C. D. Wright, 1994 October 21; digital audio tape (Box 12, Audio-cassette UA10030003-DAT-0010)
    - Talking Books: Elizabeth Cox, 1993; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0050)
    - Talking Books: Elizabeth Cox, 1993; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0051)
    - Talking Books: Gerald Barrax, 1993 June 25; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0049)
    - Talking Books: Tim McLaurin, 1993; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0052)
    - Talking Books: Tim McLaurin, 1993; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0053)
    - The Awakening, 1978 July 23; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0011)
    - The Awakening, 1978 July 23; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0012)
    - Vic Lukas: Orientation, 1982; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0036)
    - Vic Lukas: Orientation, 1982; 1/4-inch (Box 11, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0037)
    - What Makes Duke so Special, 1988 November 12; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0074)
    - What Makes Duke so Special, 1988 November 12; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0075)
  - Alumni Lecture Series, 1986-1988, undated; 2.3
    - Alex Roland, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0061)
      1 sound tape reel (52 min., 40 sec.): 10 in.
    - Alex Roland: The Manned Space Program, 1988; audiocassette (Box 12, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0020)
      reference copy: UA2003-23-5
    - Alumni Tape, Side A, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0062)
    - Alumni Tape, Side B, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0063)
    - Charlie Braswell Intros, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0054)
    - Eric Meyers, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0058)
      1 sound tape reel (45 min., 20 sec.): 10 in.
    - Eric Meyers: Judaism and Christianity, 1988; audiocassette (Box 12, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0017)
      reference copy: UA2003-23-2
    - Keith Brodie Intros, 1987 September 14; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0055)
    - Lee Iacocca / Ted Koppel: Commencement Address, 1986, 1987; audiocassette (Box 12, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0016)
      reference copy: UA2003-23-1
    - Lee Iacocca: Commencement Address, 1986; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0056)
      1 sound tape reel (25 min., 16 sec.): 7 in.
    - Orrin Pilkey, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0059)
      1 sound tape reel (42 min., 23 sec.): 10 in.
    - Orrin Pilkey: The Changing Seashore, 1988; audiocassette (Box 12, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0018)
      reference copy: UA2003-23-3
    - Reynolds Price, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0060)
      1 sound tape reel (56 min., 21 sec.): 10 in.
    - Reynolds Price: Selected Readings, undated; audiocassette (Box 12, Audio-cassette UA10030003-CS-0019)
      reference copy: UA2003-23-4
    - Ted Koppel: Commencement Address, 1987; 1/4-inch (Box 12, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0057)
      1 sound tape reel (18 min., 25 sec.): 7 in.
  - Musical Recordings, 1963-1990, undated; 2.4
    - Bill Wilkerson: One Real Folly, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0099)
    - Dan Locklair: Visions in the Haze, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 16, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0123)
    - Dan Locklair: Visions in the Haze, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 16, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0124)
    - Dave Landers, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 14, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0107)
    - Dave Landers: Demo, 1983 December; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0085)
    - Dave Landers: Rough Mixes, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0086)
    - Dave Landers: Rough Mixes, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0087)
    - Duke University Concert Band, 1963 April 15; 1/4-inch (Box 15, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0109)
    - Duke University Concert Band, 1964 April 15; 1/4-inch (Box 15, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0110)
    - Duke University Concert Band, 1964 April 15; 1/4-inch (Box 15, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0111)
    - Duke University Concert Band, 1964 October 16; 1/4-inch (Box 15, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0112)
    - Duke University Concert Band, 1964 December 13; 1/4-inch (Box 15, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0113)
    - Duke University Concert Band, 1964 December; 1/4-inch (Box 15, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0114)
    - Duke University Concert Band, 1964 December; 1/4-inch (Box 15, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0115)
    - Duke University Concert Band, circa 1964; 1/4-inch (Box 15, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0116)
    - Duke University Concert Band, circa 1964; 1/4-inch (Box 15, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0117)
    - Duke University Symphony, 1965 March 18; 1/4-inch (Box 15, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0118)
    - Duke University Symphony, 1965 March 18; 1/4-inch (Box 15, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0119)
    - Eno Experience, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0078)
    - Eno Experience, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0079)
    - Francis Perry: Page Auditorium, 1980 May 21; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0095)
    - Jim Legg: Disco Music, 1987 November 22; 1/4-inch (Box 16, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0122)
    - Joey Howell: Demo, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 14, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0103)
    - Kneewalkers: Demo, 1984 February; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0082)
    - Ladyslipper, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0083)
    - Ladyslipper, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0084)
    - Ladyslipper, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 14, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0105)
    - Ladyslipper, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 14, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0106)
    - Linz Audain: piano/voice demo, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 14, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0100)
    - Lori Koenigsberg: Demo, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 14, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0104)
    - M M & L: Demo, 1983 July 10; 1/4-inch (Box 16, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0125)
    - Mark Epperson: Demo, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0080)
    - Martin: Demo, 1983 August; 1/4-inch (Box 16, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0126)
    - Michael Ching: Durham, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 14, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0101)
    - Michael Ching: Durham, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 14, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0102)
    - Moods of Rhythm, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0089)
    - Moods of Rhythm, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0090)
    - Music for Organ and Strings, 1964 March 22; 1/4-inch (Box 16, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0127)
    - Music for Organ and Strings, 1964 March 22; 1/4-inch (Box 16, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0128)
    - Nancy Patterson: Senior Recital, 1990 January 26; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0094)
    - Nat Martin, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0088)
    - One Real Band [sic]: Demo, 1980 March; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0091)
    - One Real Band [sic]: Don't Kid Yourself, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0092)
    - One Reel Band: Demo, reference dub, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0093)
    - Rainey Reel, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0131)
    - Richard Rendleman, 1982 January; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0096)
    - Richard Rendleman, Piano Demo #2, 1982 June; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0097)
    - She Loves Me, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0143)
    - She Loves Me, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0144)
    - Stephanie Grosz: Junior Recital, 1984 April 21; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0081)
    - Stormin' Norman & Suzy & the Frugtones: Black and Blue, 1980 July 25; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0145)
    - Tilman Seebass, circa 1980-1990; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0132)
    - Tilman Seebass, circa 1980-1990; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0133)
    - Tilman Seebass, circa 1980-1990; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0134)
    - Tilman Seebass, circa 1980-1990; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0135)
    - Tilman Seebass, circa 1980-1990; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0136)
    - Tilman Seebass, circa 1980-1990; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0137)
    - Tilman Seebass, circa 1980-1990; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0138)
    - Tilman Seebass, circa 1980-1990; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0139)
    - Tilman Seebass, circa 1980-1990; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0140)
    - Tilman Seebass, circa 1980-1990; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0141)
    - Tilman Seebass, circa 1980-1990; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0142)
    - Vicki Oehling and Tom Funk: Demo, 1984 May; 1/4-inch (Box 16, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0129)
    - Vicki Oehling and Tom Funk: Demo, 1984 May; 1/4-inch (Box 16, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0130)
    - W. Wallace, undated; 1/4-inch (Box 13, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0098)
    - Warren Lankford, 1981 April 7; 1/4-inch (Box 14, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0108)
    - Warren Lankford: Demo, 1981 May; 1/4-inch (Box 16, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0120)
    - Warren Lankford: Voice, Piano Demos, 1981 May; 1/4-inch (Box 16, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0121)
    - X-Teens, 1980 March 13; 1/4-inch (Box 17, Audio-reel UA10030003-RR-0146)
- Accession UA2009-0035, 3
  - Ambitions Realized: A Nod to Nan, 2003 October 3; DVCAM (Box 18, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0036)
    A thank you note to Nan Keohane
  - Campaign 2000 Debate, VHS (Box 18, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0041)
    Foreign policy
  - Converging and Diverging: Science & Humanities, 2005 September 12; DVCAM (Box 18, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0042)
    Roundtable with Richard Brodhead.
  - Duke Class of 2000, betacam-sp (Box 18, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0103)
    montage of stills and music
  - Duke Town Hall Meeting with Richard Brodhead: A Duke Conversation: Making a Difference, 2007 March 6; DVCAM (Box 18, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0037)
    Multiple camera coverage, series held in Durham at Fuqua.
  - Duke Town Hall Meeting with Richard Brodhead: A Duke Conversation: Making a Difference, 2007 March 6; DVCAM (Box 18, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0038)
  - Excerpts from Price of Academic Freedom, mini-dv (Box 18, Video-cassette UA10030003-MiniDV-0004)
    Highlights
  - French Science Center Dedication, 2007 November 9; DVCAM (Box 18, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0041)
    Official ceremony
  - John Hope Franklin Celebration of Life, 2009 June 11; DVCAM (Box 18, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0041)
    Vernon Jordan and President Bill Clinton speeches only.
  - John Hope Franklin Celebration of Life, 2009 June 11; DVD (Box 18, Video-disc UA10030003-OP-0002)
  - Price of Academic Freedom, 2004 March 1; mini-dv (Box 18, Video-cassette UA10030003-MiniDV-0002)
  - Price of Academic Freedom, 2004 March 1; mini-dv (Box 18, Video-cassette UA10030003-MiniDV-0003)
  - Public Speech, Richard Brodhead, 2005 March 22; DVCAM (Box 18, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0039)
    Talk to undergraduates regarding protests over fair wages/labor.
- Accession UA2011-0007, 4
  - 17th Annual Service of Commemoration, MLK, 2006 January 15; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0049)
  - 17th Annual Service of Commemoration, MLK, 2006 January 15; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0050)
  - A Conversation with Two Duke University Presidents: Nannerl Keohane and Richard Brodhead, moderated by Judy Woodruff, 2004 February 1; betacam (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0104)
  - A Conversation with Two Duke University Presidents: Nannerl Keohane and Richard Brodhead, moderated by Judy Woodruff, 2004 February 1; betacam (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0105)
  - Alumni War Memorial Dedication, 2009 October 23; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0057)
  - Announcement of Richard H. Brodhead, New President of Duke University, Rare Book Room, cut version, undated; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0042)
  - Carl Rove, Page Auditorium, 2007 December 3; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0052)
  - Convocation, Duke Chapel, 2009 August 19; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0055)
  - Deliberations, Griffith Theater, 2008 October 24; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0053)